http://crownlabel.com/privacy-terms/

Privacy & Terms – Crown Label
CALL OR EMAIL US FOR A QUOTE:
Press enter to begin your search
No menu assigned!
PRIVACY POLICIES
Crown Label Company will not sell or provide any personal information to anyone without your permission. We are committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our website. Moreover, we will never use any personal information collected at this site for any purpose other than internal use, unless the registrant chooses to be added to mailing lists (this is a choice made by the registrant on the Registration form).
The following is an explanation of the types of information that are collected from visitors at this site.
Anonymous Information – Crown Label Company will track visitor activity to our site using IP addresses and set temporary cookies to track user sessions. This data helps us keep track of the number of visitors and help facilitate the dynamic nature of our site. This information is not connected in any way with personal information (name, address, etc.). The user’s identity remains anonymous with this type of information.
Registration information is stored in a database on a secure server. The database is password protected and is only accessible by Crown Label Company servers and authorized personnel of Crown Label Company.
Third-Party Privacy Policies
Please be aware that other websites that may be accessed through our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those third-party web sites linked to Crown Label Company web site are not covered by this privacy statement.
To ask us any questions about our privacy policy, contact our label manufacturing company at (657) 231-4802 in Santa Ana, CA.
TERMS & CONDITIONS
Please check back soon for more details on our Terms & Conditions. In the meantime, please contact us for more details.
3720-24 W Warner Ave.
Santa Ana, CA 92704
Our Location
© 2020 Crown Label.
